JACK MIDDLETON

CHEF DE PARTIE | FRONT-END WEB DEV

ABOUT ME

Since leaving school with 13 GCSE qualifications, I have built up a portfolio of experience in the hospitality sector working at Butlins and Loungers in Monmouth and then Swansea, and then returning to London to work at The Shangri-La Hotel at The Shard, as well as Le Caprice and Chiltern Firehouse. Outside of work I play drums in a band, and have recently started nurturing a long-term interest in IT, recently finishing a beginner course in HTML, CSS and JavaScript frontend development, and working on a freelance basis at Wisp Creative, a boutique web design agency based in London. My experience has nurtured my skills in time management, team-work, and working under intense pressure and to deadlines. I would now like the opportunity to use and develop these skills as part of a new team.

SKILLS

Working under pressure in an intense environment, time management, team work, team management, hospitality, customer service, creativity, enthusiasm, determination, passion, organisation, detail oriented.

CONTACT INFO:

Mobile: 07802242378

Email: jackmiddleton96@hotmail.co.uk Address: Flat 14, Toulouse Court, 2 Rossetti Road, London SE16 3EA

RFFFRFNCFS

Available on request.

A self-motivated entry level software dev, I've recently created a blog using Django, Python and Bootstrap that can be found at Jackmiddleton.pythonanywhere.com. I've been using a variety of sources to further my learning such as Django-girls, Udemy and codeacademy. My current project is an initiative tracker which I intend to create using a python based CLI and Django front-end, hosting a repository on Github and the app on pythonanywhere. Over the course of my studies I have developed a basic understanding of the Languages/Frameworks, Tools and Methods below.

Programming Languages/Frameworks: Python3.8, Django, HTML, CSS, JavaScript Tools: Git Methods: Agile

EXPERIENCE

Chef De Partie

The Shangri-La Hotel at The Shard | Feb 2020 - Present

- In charge of the Larder section and responsible for 9 other chefs, across all sections, and ensuring the speed and quality of food is to the correct standard.
- I have developed my team management skills, holding a supervisor role to junior colleagues, and also working closely with the head chef, learning how to create menu worthy dishes with several having made their way on to menu.

Chef De Partie

Le Caprice | Oct 2019 - Feb 2020

- Managed the Garnish section.
- Learnt more team management skills here as I looked after 4 juniors on my section, as well as aiding the apprentices' learning.
- Ensured all food was the correct quality and went out in a timely fashion.
- Left after a brief period to return to the Shangri-la as Le Caprice closed down.

Demi-Chef de Partie

Chiltern Firehouse | June 2019 - Oct 2019

- I learnt how to handle large volumes of customers at one time, as the restaurant was at full capacity almost every service.

Demi-Chef de Partie

The Shangri-La Hotel at The Shard | Aug 2018 - June 2019

- Started as a Commis Chef and over the course of 6 months I developed the skills necessary to become a Demi-Chef de Partie.
- Learning how to run a section, supervise junior members of staff and ensure everything was executed to the correct level of quality.

Further experience available on request.

EDUCATION

Brentwood County High School

2006 - 2011

GCSE

A*-C (10 qualifications)

Beginner Python Programming Course

2021

Tim Buchalka's Learm Programming Academy

Beginner Certification Course in CSS, HTML, JavaScript

2021

YouAccel